bestseohub.com 2019-07-22

# Privacy Policy

##### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsfeed or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information or you may, however, visit our site anonymously.

##### How may we use the information we collect?

We use the information that we collect to improve the overall quality of your experience with the Sites and Services, and to facilitate evaluation, improvement, and development of the Services. We aggregate query information for internal reporting purposes and optimization of advertising revenue.

##### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell,trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

##### Disclaimer

All the information on this website is published in good faith and for general information purpose only. BestSeoHub.com does not make any warranties about the completeness, reliability and accuracy of this information. Any action you take upon the information you find on this website (BestSeoHub.com), is strictly at your own risk. We will not be liable for any losses and/or damages in connection with the use of our website.

##### Purchasing Services

If you purchase services from us, we will ask for the minimum information necessary to verify that you are authorized to make the purchase, that you are who you say, and not someone else with your credit card. If you notice any charges from our site that you did not authorize, please contact us so we can resolve any issues.

##### Cookies

A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows us to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and we does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds

##### Contact Us

If you have any questions relating to our privacy policy, please contact us
